<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<body>
	<article>
	<title>Lysosomal alpha-mannosidase and alpha-mannosidosis.</title>
	<abstract>Lysosomal alpha-mannosidase with acidic pH optimum is ubiquitous in human tissues where is expressed in two major forms, A and B that are the product of a single gene located on chromosome 19. Mutations in the gene encoding for alpha-mannosidase cause alpha- mannosidosis, an autosomal recessive disease, resulting in the accumulation of unprocessed mannose containing oligosaccharide material. This rare disease has an estimated incidence of 1/500.0.00 live births and clinically is divided into three subgroups. Today the most promising therapy for this disease is the enzyme replacement therapy. To develop this strategy a mouse model for alpha-mannosidosis has been generated and a recombinant human alpha-mannosidase has been produced from Chinese-hamster ovary cells. Interestingly it has been shown that the recombinant enzyme, used in high dose, can cross the blood brain barrier. This recombinant enzyme has been tested in the first randomized study investigating the efficacy of enzyme replacement therapy in patients with alpha-mannosidosis. This review contains the scientific progresses on lysosomal alpha-mannosidase from the cloning to the beginning of the therapy.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>The Central Nervous System and the Gut Microbiome.</title>
	<abstract>Neurodevelopment is a complex process governed by both intrinsic and extrinsic signals. While historically studied by researching the brain, inputs from the periphery impact many neurological conditions. Indeed, emerging data suggest communication between the gut and the brain in anxiety, depression, cognition, and autism spectrum disorder (ASD). The development of a healthy, functional brain depends on key pre- and post-natal events that integrate environmental cues, such as molecular signals from the gut. These cues largely originate from the microbiome, the consortium of symbiotic bacteria that reside within all animals. Research over the past few years reveals that the gut microbiome plays a role in basic neurogenerative processes such as the formation of the blood-brain barrier, myelination, neurogenesis, and microglia maturation and also modulates many aspects of animal behavior. Herein, we discuss the biological intersection of neurodevelopment and the microbiome and explore the hypothesis that gut bacteria are integral contributors to development and function of the nervous system and to the balance between mental health and disease.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>A Functional Genomics Approach to Understand Variation in Cytokine Production in Humans.</title>
	<abstract>As part of the Human Functional Genomics Project, which aims to understand the factors that determine the variability of immune responses, we investigated genetic variants affecting cytokine production in response to ex vivo stimulation in two independent cohorts of 500 and 200 healthy individuals. We demonstrate a strong impact of genetic heritability on cytokine production capacity after challenge with bacterial, fungal, viral, and non-microbial stimuli. In addition to 17 novel genome-wide significant cytokine QTLs (cQTLs), our study provides a comprehensive picture of the genetic variants that influence six different cytokines in whole blood, blood mononuclear cells, and macrophages. Important biological pathways that contain cytokine QTLs map to pattern recognition receptors (TLR1-6-10 cluster), cytokine and complement inhibitors, and the kallikrein system. The cytokine QTLs show enrichment for monocyte-specific enhancers, are more often located in regions under positive selection, and are significantly enriched among SNPs associated with infections and immune-mediated diseases.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Computational biomechanics of human red blood cells in hematological disorders.</title>
	<abstract>We review recent advances in multiscale modeling of the biomechanical characteristics of red blood cells (RBCs) in hematological diseases, and their relevance to the structure and dynamics of defective RBCs. We highlight examples of successful simulations of blood disorders including malaria and other hereditary disorders, such as sickle-cell anemia, spherocytosis and elliptocytosis.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Vascular dysfunction-associated with Alzheimer's disease.</title>
	<abstract>Our attention is focused on the study of a new model based on the red blood cell (RBC) and on its interaction with amyloid beta peptide 1-42 (AB). RBC are highly deformable to assist blood flow in the microcirculation. For this reasons RBC abnormalities could contribute to Alzheimer's disease (AD) by obstructing oxygen delivery to brain, causing hypoxia. In our work, considering that RBC membrane contains, among blood elements, higher acetylcholinesterase (AChE) levels, we can assume that in blood occurs a mechanism similar to the one which occurs at the neuronal level leading to an increase of AB toxicity mediated by its binding with AChE, located on the RBC external face. Furthermore, since mechanical properties of RBC membrane are regulated by a number of molecular components of signalling and/or regulatory pathways, of these, particular interest has been addressed toward Nitric Oxide (NO) metabolism, due to its dependence to AChE.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Influence of nanoporous poly (ether imide) particle extracts on human aortic endothelial cells (HAECs).</title>
	<abstract>Accumulated uremic toxins like indoxyl sulphate, hippuric acid and p-cresyl sulphates in renal failure patients stimulate proinflammatory effects, and consequently kidney and cardiovascular diseases. Low clearance rate of these uremic toxins from the blood of uremic patients by convention techniques like hemodialysis is due to their strong covalent albumin binding (greater than 95%) and hydrophobic nature, which led to alternatives like usage of hydrophobic adsorber's in removing these toxins from the plasma of kidney patients. Usage of biodegradable synthetic polymers as hydrophobic adsorbers has taken centre stage for their wide range of biomedical applications in the form of medical devices. Applications of polymers range from tissue engineering to drug delivery, abundance and special features like tissue engineering provided a great boon for their valuable therapeutic applications. Polymers like polyethylene, polyurethane, polymethylmethacrylate, cellophane and polytetrafluoroethylene were already in use as substitutes for metal devices as dialysis membranes. Among new crop of synthetic polymers, one such ideal adsorbed material are highly porous micro particles of poly(etherimide) (PEI) with an average diameter of 50-180 um and porosity around 88 2% prepared by spraying and coagulation process.It is essential to make sure that these synthetic polymers should not evoke any inflammatory or apoptotic response during dialysis. Therefore in our study we evaluated in vitro effect of PEI microparticle extracts in HAECs concerning toxicity, inflammation and apoptosis. No cell toxicity was observed when HAECs were treated with PEI extracts and inflammatory/apoptotic markers were not upregulated in presence of PEI extracts. Our results ensures biocompatibility of PEI particles and further hemocompatibility of particles will be tested.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Transgenic mouse model of IgM+ lymphoproliferative disease mimicking Waldenstrom macroglobulinemia.</title>
	<abstract>Waldenstrom macroglobulinemia (WM) is a low-grade incurable immunoglobulin M+ (IgM+) lymphoplasmacytic lymphoma for which a genetically engineered mouse model of de novo tumor development is lacking. On the basis of evidence that the pro-inflammatory cytokine, interleukin 6 (IL6), and the survival-enhancing oncoprotein, B cell leukemia 2 (BCL2), have critical roles in the natural history of WM, we hypothesized that the enforced expression of IL6 and BCL2 in mice unable to perform immunoglobulin class switch recombination may result in a lymphoproliferative disease that mimics WM. To evaluate this possibility, we generated compound transgenic BALB/c mice that harbored the human BCL2 and IL6 transgenes, EuSV-BCL2-22 and H2-Ld-hIL6, on the genetic background of activation-induced cytidine deaminase (AID) deficiency. We designated these mice BCL2+IL6+AID- and found that they developed-with full genetic penetrance (100% incidence) and suitably short latency (93 days median survival)-a severe IgM+ lymphoproliferative disorder that recapitulated important features of human WM. However, the BCL2+IL6+AID- model also exhibited shortcomings, such as low serum IgM levels and histopathological changes not seen in patients with WM, collectively indicating that further refinements of the model are required to achieve better correlations with disease characteristics of WM.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Citrate metabolism in red blood cells stored in additive solution-3.</title>
	<abstract>BACKGROUND:
	Red blood cells (RBCs) are thought to have a relatively simple metabolic network compared to other human cell types. Recent proteomics reports challenge the notion that RBCs are mere hemoglobin carriers with limited metabolic activity. Expanding our understanding of RBC metabolism has key implications in many biomedical areas, including transfusion medicine.
	STUDY DESIGN AND METHODS:
	In-gel digestion coupled with mass spectrometric analysis proteomics approaches were combined with state-of-the-art tracing experiments by incubating leukofiltered RBCs in additive solution-3 for up to 42 days under blood bank conditions, in presence of 13 C1,2,3 -glucose, 2,2,4,4-d-citrate, and 13 C,15 N-glutamine.
	RESULTS:
	Results indicate that the pentose phosphate pathway/glycolysis ratio increases during storage in additive solution-3. While the majority of supernatant glucose is consumed to fuel glycolysis, incorporation of glucose-derived pentose phosphate moieties was observed in nucleoside monophosphates. Incubation with deuterated citrate indicated that citrate uptake and metabolism contribute to explain the origin of up to approximately 20% to 30% lactate that could not be explained by glucose oxidation and 2,3-diphosphoglycerate consumption alone. Incubation with 13 C,15 N-glutamine showed that glutaminolysis fuels transamination reactions and accumulation of millimolar levels of 5-oxoproline, while de novo glutathione synthesis was not significantly active during refrigerated storage.
	CONCLUSION:
	Quantitative tracing metabolic experiments revealed that mature RBCs can metabolize other substrates than glucose, such as citrate, an observation relevant to transfusion medicine (i.e., formulation of novel additives), and other research endeavors where metabolic modulation of RBCs opens potential avenues for therapeutic interventions, such as in sickle cell disease.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Disease etiology and diagnosis by TCR repertoire analysis goes viral.</title>
	<abstract>The importance of T-cell receptor (TCR) repertoire diversity is highlighted in murine models of immunodeficiency and in many human pathologies. However, the true extent of TCR diversity and how this diversity varies in health and disease is poorly understood. In a previous issue of the European Journal of Immunology, Lossius et al. [Eur. J. Immunol. 2014. 44: 3439-3452] dissected the composition of the TCR repertoire in the context of multiple sclerosis (MS) using high-throughput sequencing of TCR-b chains in cerebrospinal fluid samples and blood. The authors demonstrated that the TCR repertoire of the CSF was largely distinct from the blood and enriched in EBV-reactive CD8+ T cells in MS patients. Studies of this kind have long been hindered by technical limitations and remain scarce in the literature. However, TCR sequencing methodologies are progressing apace and will undoubtedly shed light on the genetic basis of T-cell responses and the ontogeny of T-cell-mediated diseases, such as MS.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Involvement of Programmed Cell Death in Neurotoxicity of Metallic Nanoparticles: Recent Advances and Future Perspectives.</title>
	<abstract>The widespread application of metallic nanoparticles (NPs) or NP-based products has increased the risk of exposure to NPs in humans. The brain is an important organ that is more susceptible to exogenous stimuli. Moreover, any impairment to the brain is irreversible. Recently, several in vivo studies have found that metallic NPs can be absorbed into the animal body and then translocated into the brain, mainly through the blood-brain barrier and olfactory pathway after systemic administration. Furthermore, metallic NPs can cross the placental barrier to accumulate in the fetal brain, causing developmental neurotoxicity on exposure during pregnancy. Therefore, metallic NPs become a big threat to the brain. However, the mechanisms underlying the neurotoxicity of metallic NPs remain unclear. Programmed cell death (PCD), which is different from necrosis, is defined as active cell death and is regulated by certain genes. PCD can be mainly classified into apoptosis, autophagy, necroptosis, and pyroptosis. It is involved in brain development, neurodegenerative disorders, psychiatric disorders, and brain injury. Given the pivotal role of PCD in neurological functions, we reviewed relevant articles and tried to summarize the recent advances and future perspectives of PCD involvement in the neurotoxicity of metallic NPs, with the purpose of comprehensively understanding the neurotoxic mechanisms of NPs.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Artificial Blood Substitutes: First Steps on the Long Route to Clinical Utility.</title>
	<abstract>The 21st century is challenging for human beings. Increased population growth, population aging, generation of new infectious agents, and natural disasters are some threatening factors for the current state of blood transfusion. However, it seems that science and technology not only could overcome these challenges but also would turn many human dreams to reality in this regard. Scientists believe that one of the future evolutionary innovations could be artificial blood substitutes that might pave the way to a new era in transfusion medicine. In this review, recent status and progresses in artificial blood substitutes, focusing on red blood cells substitutes, are summarized. In addition, steps taken toward the development of artificial blood technology and some of their promises and hurdles will be highlighted. However, it must be noted that artificial blood is still at the preliminary stages of development, and to fulfill this dream, ie, to routinely transfuse artificial blood into human vessels, we still have to strengthen our knowledge and be patient.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>JAK2 V617F Mutation in Adult T Cell Leukemia-Lymphoma.
	</title>
	<abstract>Adult T cell Leukemia/lymphoma (ATL) is a mature T-cell neoplasm that has strong association with the human T-lymphotropic virus type 1 (HTLV-I) infection. This infection is endemic in our region (north eastern Iran). It has been highlighted that Janus Kinase family proteins and specially JAK2 mutations have a pivotal role in the development of many types of hematological malignancies and in particular myeloproliferative neoplasms. So far, the underlying molecular mechanisms leading to the ATL are not well understood. Therefore, in this study it was hypothesized that JAK2 (V617F) mutation may be present in samples from patients with ATL. This case control study was performed in north-eastern Iran. Using polymerase chain reaction, JAK2 (V617F) mutation was performed in 20 DNA samples from ATL patients and 20 HTLV-1 asymptomatic carriers (control group). The results of ATL subjects and the control group were compared by using SPSS software. In the case group 13 (65 %) and 7 patients (35 %) were male and female respectively, with the age range between 40 and 80 years. Only one patients has JAK2 mutation and this mutation was absent in 95 % of ATL patients as well as the HTLV-1 asymptomatic carriers. The results of our study demonstrated that JAK2 V617F mutation is not a common phenomenon in ATL. However, further studies are required to investigate the possible dysregulation of JAK signaling in ATL.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>The Synergistic Effects of Decitabine Combined with Arsenic Trioxide (ATO) in the Human Myelodysplastic Syndrome Cell Line SKM-1.</title>
	<abstract>Despite recent advances in the treatment of myelodysplastic syndrome (MDS), single-agent clinical effects remain unsatisfactory, and decitabine monotherapy is also associated with a relatively low rate of complete remission. To study the combined effects and mechanism of decitabine (DAC) and arsenic trioxide (ATO) on the human myelodysplastic cell line SKM-1,we used the MTS assay and CalcuSyn software to determine the cytotoxicity and potential synergistic effects, respectively. Furthermore, we determined apoptosis and measured the mRNA expression level of two genes that are considered main regulators of the apoptosis process. The results showed that DAC and/or ATO can inhibit the proliferation of SKM-1 cells and demonstrated significant synergy between the two agents. Additionally, combination of 2.5 umol/L DAC and 5 umol/L ATO led to a significantly higher apoptosis rate and more significantly decreased the Bcl2/Bax ratio than either compound alone. Based on the observations of this study, we suggest that combined administration of these two drugs might be considered a novel therapeutic regimen for treating MDS.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Chronic Myelocytic Leukemia (CML) Patient-Derived Dendritic Cells Transfected with Autologous Total RNA Induces CML-Specific Cytotoxicity.</title>
	<abstract>The oncogenic bcr/abl1 fusion gene is a chronic myelogenous leukemia (CML)-specific antigen which is absent in normal tissues. This makes bcr/abl1 a perfect target for developing CML vaccines that elicit specific immune responses against minimal residual disease while sparing normal tissue. The aim of this study was to use different methods to induce dendritic cells (DCs) derived from patients with CML (CML-DCs) and analyze them for CML-specific tumor cytotoxicity for immune therapy. Bone marrow-derived mononuclear cells from ten CML patients were studied to induce CML-DC differentiation in the presence of recombinant human interleukin-4, rh-granulocyte-macrophage-colony stimulating factor, and tumor necrosis factor-alpha with either a total RNA-lipofectamine complex, total RNA or CML tumor lysate (freeze-thawed). CML-DC maturation, confirmed by expression of CD1, CD40, CD80, CD83, CD86 and by real-time polymerase chain reaction, validated the CML-origin of these DC cells. CML-DCs stimulated cytotoxic T-cell (CTL) apoptosis, high levels of IL-12 secretion, and had significant inhibitory effect on K562 tumorigenicity in nude mice. CML-DCs pulsed with total RNA by lipofectamine transfection produced the strongest effect in tumor-specific CTL functions. These results indicate that CML-DCs transfected with total RNA by lipofectamine induce the strongest CTL cytotoxicity and have the greatest potential for CML immune therapy. This study holds promise for a DC-based strategy for inducing anti-leukemia responses and establishes a foundation for developing RNA vaccination against CML.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Imprime PGG-Mediated Anti-Cancer Immune Activation Requires Immune Complex Formation.</title>
	<abstract>Imprime PGG (Imprime), an intravenously-administered, soluble B-glucan, has shown compelling efficacy in multiple phase 2 clinical trials with tumor targeting or anti-angiogenic antibodies. Mechanistically, Imprime acts as pathogen-associated molecular pattern (PAMP) directly activating innate immune effector cells, triggering a coordinated anti-cancer immune response. Herein, using whole blood from healthy human subjects, we show that Imprime-induced anti-cancer functionality is dependent on immune complex formation with naturally-occurring, anti-B glucan antibodies (ABA). The formation of Imprime-ABA complexes activates complement, primarily via the classical complement pathway, and is opsonized by iC3b. Immune complex binding depends upon Complement Receptor 3 and Fcg Receptor IIa, eliciting phenotypic activation of, and enhanced chemokine production by, neutrophils and monocytes, enabling these effector cells to kill antibody-opsonized tumor cells via the generation of reactive oxygen species and antibody-dependent cellular phagocytosis. Importantly, these innate immune cell changes were not evident in subjects with low ABA levels but could be rescued with exogenous ABA supplementation. Together, these data indicate that pre-existing ABA are essential for Imprime-mediated anti-cancer immune activation and suggest that pre-treatment ABA levels may provide a plausible patient selection biomarker to delineate patients most likely to benefit from Imprime-based therapy.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Probing Intracellular Element Concentration Changes during Neutrophil Extracellular Trap Formation Using Synchrotron Radiation Based X-Ray Fluorescence.</title>
	<abstract>High pressure frozen (HPF), cryo-substituted microtome sections of 2 um thickness containing human neutrophils (white blood cells) were analyzed using synchrotron radiation based X-ray fluorescence (SR nano-XRF) at a spatial resolution of 50 nm. Besides neutrophils from a control culture, we also analyzed neutrophils stimulated for 1-2 h with phorbol myristate acetate (PMA), a substance inducing the formation of so-called Neutrophil Extracellular Traps (or NETs), a defense system again pathogens possibly involving proteins with metal chelating properties. In order to gain insight in metal transport during this process, precise local evaluation of elemental content was performed reaching limits of detection (LODs) of 1 ppb. Mean weight fractions within entire neutrophils, their nuclei and cytoplasms were determined for the three main elements P, S and Cl, but also for the 12 following trace elements: K, Ca, Mn, Fe, Co, Ni, Cu, Zn, Se, Br, Sr and Pb. Statistical analysis, including linear regression provided objective analysis and a measure for concentration changes. The nearly linear Ca and Cl concentration changes in neutrophils could be explained by already known phenomena such as the induction of Ca channels and the uptake of Cl under activation of NET forming neutrophils. Linear concentration changes were also found for P, S, K, Mn, Fe, Co and Se. The observed linear concentration increase for Mn could be related to scavenging of this metal from the pathogen by means of the neutrophil protein calprotectin, whereas the concentration increase of Se may be related to its antioxidant function protecting neutrophils from the reactive oxygen species they produce against pathogens. We emphasize synchrotron radiation based nanoscopic X-ray fluorescence as an enabling analytical technique to study changing (trace) element concentrations throughout cellular processes, provided accurate sample preparation and data-analysis.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Identifying Early Target Cells of Nipah Virus Infection in Syrian Hamsters.</title>
	<abstract>BACKGROUND:
	Nipah virus causes respiratory and neurologic disease with case fatality rates up to 100% in individual outbreaks. End stage lesions have been described in the respiratory and nervous systems, vasculature and often lymphoid organs in fatal human cases; however, the initial target organs of Nipah virus infection have not been identified. Here, we detected the initial target tissues and cells of Nipah virus and tracked virus dissemination during the early phase of infection in Syrian hamsters inoculated with a Nipah virus isolate from Malaysia (NiV-M) or Bangladesh (NiV-B).
	METHODOLOGY/PRINCIPAL FINDINGS:
	Syrian hamsters were euthanized between 4 and 48 hours post intranasal inoculation and tissues were collected and analyzed for the presence of viral RNA, viral antigen and infectious virus. Virus replication was first detected at 8 hours post inoculation (hpi). Nipah virus initially targeted type I pneumocytes, bronchiolar respiratory epithelium and alveolar macrophages in the lung and respiratory and olfactory epithelium lining the nasal turbinates. By 16 hpi, virus disseminated to epithelial cells lining the larynx and trachea. Although the pattern of viral dissemination was similar for both virus isolates, the rate of spread was slower for NiV-B. Infectious virus was not detected in the nervous system or blood and widespread vascular infection and lesions within lymphoid organs were not observed, even at 48 hpi.
	CONCLUSIONS/SIGNIFICANCE:
	Nipah virus initially targets the respiratory system. Virus replication in the brain and infection of blood vessels in non-respiratory tissues does not occur during the early phase of infection. However, virus replicates early in olfactory epithelium and may serve as the first step towards nervous system dissemination, suggesting that development of vaccines that block virus dissemination or treatments that can access the brain and spinal cord and directly inhibit virus replication may be necessary for preventing central nervous system pathology.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Retargeted Foamy Virus Vectors Integrate Less Frequently Near Proto-oncogenes.
	</title>
	<abstract>Retroviral gene therapy offers immense potential to treat many genetic diseases and has already shown efficacy in clinical trials. However, retroviral vector mediated genotoxicity remains a major challenge and clinically relevant approaches to reduce integration near genes and proto-oncogenes are needed. Foamy retroviral vectors have several advantages over gammaretroviral and lentiviral vectors including a potentially safer integration profile and a lower propensity to activate nearby genes. Here we successfully retargeted foamy retroviral vectors away from genes and into satellite regions enriched for trimethylated histone H3 at lysine 9 by modifying the foamy virus Gag and Pol proteins. Retargeted foamy retroviral vectors integrated near genes and proto-oncogenes less often than controls. Importantly, retargeted foamy retroviral vectors can be produced at high, clinically relevant titers, and unlike other reported retargeting approaches engineered target cells are not needed to achieve retargeting. As proof of principle for use in the clinic we show efficient transduction and retargeting in human cord blood CD34+ cells. The modified Gag and Pol helper constructs we describe will allow any investigator to simply use these helper plasmids during vector production to retarget therapeutic foamy retroviral vectors.</abstract>
	</article>

	<article>
	<title>Long-term exposure to Myozyme results in a decrease of anti-drug antibodies in late-onset Pompe disease patients.</title>
	<abstract>Immunogenicity of recombinant human acid-alpha glucosidase (rhGAA) in enzyme replacement therapy (ERT) is a safety and efficacy concern in the management of late-onset Pompe disease (LOPD). However, long-term effects of ERT on humoral and cellular responses to rhGAA are still poorly understood. To better understand the impact of immunogenicity of rhGAA on the efficacy of ERT, clinical data and blood samples from LOPD patients undergoing ERT for 4 years  or untreated  were collected and analyzed. In treated LOPD patients, anti-rhGAA antibodies peaked within the first 1000 days of ERT, while long-term exposure to rhGAA resulted in clearance of antibodies with residual production of non-neutralizing IgG. Analysis of T cell responses to rhGAA showed detectable T cell reactivity only after in vitro restimulation. Upregulation of several cytokines and chemokines was detectable in both treated and untreated LOPD subjects, while IL2 secretion was detectable only in subjects who received ERT. These results indicate that long-term ERT in LOPD patients results in a decrease in antibody titers and residual production of non-inhibitory IgGs. Immune responses to GAA following long-term ERT do not seem to affect efficacy of ERT and are consistent with an immunomodulatory effect possibly mediated by regulatory T cells.</abstract>
	</article>
	</body>