<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<body>
	<movie>
		<title>BILLY LYNN'S LONG HALFTIME WALK SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>Three-time Academy Award winner Ang Lee brings his extraordinary vision to Billy Lynn's Long Halftime Walk, based on the widely-acclaimed, bestselling novel.  The film is told from the point of view of 19-year-old private Billy Lynn (newcomer Joe Alwyn) who, along with his fellow soldiers in Bravo Squad, becomes a hero after a harrowing Iraq battle and is brought home temporarily for a victory tour.  Through flashbacks, culminating at the spectacular halftime show of the Thanksgiving Day football game, the film reveals what really happened to the squad - contrasting the realities of the war with America's perceptions.  The film also stars Kristen Stewart, Chris Tucker, Garrett Hedlund, with Vin Diesel, and Steve Martin. Lee used new technology, shooting at an ultra-high frame rate for the first time in film history, to create an immersive digital experience helping him dramatize war in a way never seen before. </description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>ARRIVAL SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>ARRIVAL is a provocative science fiction thriller from acclaimed director Denis Villeneuve. When mysterious spacecraft touch down across the globe, an elite team - lead by expert linguist Louise Banks (Amy Adams) - are brought together to investigate. As mankind teeters on the verge of global war, Banks and the team race against time for answers -- and to find them, she will take a chance that could threaten her life, and quite possibly humanity.</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>SHUT IN SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>A woman discovers a terrifying secret about her troubled son. </description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>THE EDGE OF SEVENTEEN SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>Two high school girls are best friends until one dates the other's older brother, who is totally his sister's nemesis.</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>FANTASTIC BEASTS AND WHERE TO FIND THEM SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>The adventures of writer Newt Scamander in New York's secret community of witches and wizards seventy years before Harry Potter reads his book in school. </description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>NOCTURNAL ANIMALS SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>From writer/director Tom Ford comes a haunting romantic thriller of shocking intimacy and gripping tension that explores the thin lines between love and cruelty, and revenge and redemption. Academy Award nominees Amy Adams and Jake Gyllenhaal star as a divorced couple discovering dark truths about each other and themselves in NOCTURNAL ANIMALS.</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>ALLIED SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>1942. After falling in love with a French agent during a dangerous North African mission, an Allied counter-intelligence agent is quietly notified that the woman he has married and had a baby with is likely a Nazi spy.
	</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>RULES DON'T APPLY SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>An unconventional love story of an aspiring actress, her determined driver, and the eccentric billionaire who they work for.</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>MOANA SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>In the ancient South Pacific world of Oceania, Moana, a born navigator, sets sail in search of a fabled island. During her incredible journey, she teams up with her hero, the legendary demi-god Maui, to traverse the open ocean on an action-packed voyage, encountering enormous sea creatures, breathtaking underworlds and ancient folklore.</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>BAD SANTA 2 SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>BAD SANTA 2 returns Academy Award-winner BILLY BOB THORNTON to the screen as America's favorite anti-hero, Willie Soke. Fueled by cheap whiskey, greed and hatred, Willie teams up once again with his angry little sidekick, Marcus (TONY COX), to knock off a Chicago charity on Christmas Eve. Along for the ride is 'the kid' - chubby and cheery Thurman Merman (BRETT KELLY), a 250-pound ray of sunshine who brings out Willie's sliver of humanity.

		Mommy issues arise when the pair are joined by Academy Award, Golden Globe and Emmy-winner KATHY BATES, as Willie's horror story of a mother, Sunny Soke. A super butch super bitch, Sunny raises the bar for the gang's ambitions, while somehow lowering the standards of criminal behavior. Willie is further burdened by lusting after the curvaceous and prim Diane, played by Emmy Award-nominee CHRISTINA HENDRICKS, the charity director with a heart of gold and libido of steel.
		
		You better watch out: BAD SANTA 2 is coming to town.

		MARK WATERS directs BAD SANTA 2 from a screenplay by Johnny Rosenthal and Shauna Cross, based on characters by Glenn Ficarra and John Requa. GEYER KOSINSKI and ANDREW GUNN produce. Executive producers are Zanne Devine, David Thwaites, Gabriel Hammond, Daniel Hammond, Mark Waters, Jessica Tuchinsky, Adam Fields, and Doug Ellin. The film is a BROAD GREEN PICTURES and MIRAMAX(r) release. In theatres November 23, 2016.</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>MISS SLOANE SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>MISS SLOANE is the story a brilliant but ruthless lobbyist (Jessica Chastain) who is notorious for her unparalleled talent and her desire to win at all costs, even when it puts her own career at risk. The thriller pulls back the curtain on how Capitol Hill games are played and won as Sloane faces off against the most influential powers in D.C.</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>KIDNAP SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>A mother stops at nothing to recover her kidnapped son. </description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>JACKIE SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>JACKIE is a searing and intimate portrait of one of the most important and tragic moments in American history, seen through the eyes of the iconic First Lady, then Jacqueline Bouvier Kennedy (Natalie Portman). JACKIE places us in her world during the days immediately following her husband's assassination. Known for her extraordinary dignity and poise, here we see a psychological portrait of the First Lady as she struggles to maintain her husband's legacy and the world of "Camelot" that they created and loved so well.</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>LA LA LAND SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>La La Land, written and directed by Academy Award nominee Damien Chazelle [Whiplash], tells the story of Mia [Emma Stone], an aspiring actress, and Sebastian [Ryan Gosling], a dedicated jazz musician, struggling to make ends meet while pursuing their dreams in a city known for destroying hopes and breaking hearts. With modern day Los Angeles as the backdrop, this musical about everyday life explores what is more important: a once-in-a-lifetime love or the spotlight. </description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>INCARNATE SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>A wheelchair-bound exorcist is able to enter the subconscious minds of the possessed.
	</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>FRIEND REQUEST SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>When a college student unfriends a mysterious girl online, she finds herself fighting a demonic presence that wants to make her lonely by killing her closest friends.</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>OFFICE CHRISTMAS PARTY SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>In OFFICE CHRISTMAS PARTY, when the CEO (Jennifer Aniston) tries to close her hard-partying brother's branch, he (T.J. Miller) and his Chief Technical Officer (Jason Bateman) must rally their co-workers and host an epic office Christmas party in an effort to impress a potential client and close a sale that will save their jobs. The latest comedy from directors Josh Gordon and Will Speck (BLADES OF GLORY) co-stars Kate McKinnon, Olivia Munn, Jillian Bell, Rob Corddry, Vanessa Bayer, Randall Park, Sam Richardson, Jamie Chung, and Courtney B. Vance in the funniest movie of the holiday season.</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>COLLATERAL BEAUTY SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>When a successful New York advertising executive suffers a great tragedy he retreats from life.  While his concerned friends try desperately to reconnect with him, he seeks answers from the universe by writing letters to Love, Time and Death.  But it's not until his notes bring unexpected personal responses that he begins to understand how these constants interlock in a life fully lived, and how even the deepest loss can reveal moments of meaning and beauty.  </description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>THE SPACE BETWEEN US SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>In this interplanetary adventure, a space shuttle embarks on the first mission to colonize Mars, only to discover after takeoff that one of the astronauts is pregnant. Shortly after landing, she dies from complications while giving birth to the first human born on the red planet  never revealing who the father is. Thus begins the extraordinary life of Gardner Elliot - an inquisitive, highly intelligent boy who reaches the age of 16 having only met 14 people in his very unconventional upbringing. While searching for clues about his father, and the home planet he's never known, Gardner begins an online friendship with a street smart girl in Colorado named Tulsa. When he finally gets a chance to go to Earth, he's eager to experience all of the wonders he could only read about on Mars – from the most simple to the extraordinary. But once his explorations begin, scientists discover that Gardner's organs can't withstand Earth's atmosphere. Eager to find his father, Gardner escapes the team of scientists and joins with Tulsa on a race against time to unravel the mysteries of how he came to be, and where he belongs in the universe. </description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>SOLACE SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>A psychic works with the FBI in order to hunt down a serial killer.</description>
	</movie>

	<movie>
		<title>ROGUE ONE: A STAR WARS STORY SYNOPSIS</title>
		<description>From Lucasfilm comes the first of the Star Wars standalone films, Rogue One: A Star Wars Story, an all-new epic adventure. In a time of conflict, a group of unlikely heroes band together on a mission to steal the plans to the Death Star, the Empire’s ultimate weapon of destruction. This key event in the Star Wars timeline brings together ordinary people who choose to do extraordinary things, and in doing so, become part of something greater than themselves.</description>
	</movie>
	</body>